completecaremaintenance.com 2017-06-04

# NJ Office Cleaning Services | Warehouse Cleaning Services

### Privacy Policy

* * *

Complete Care Maintenance (we” or “us”) values its visitors’ privacy. This privacy policy is effective March 21, 2015; it summarizes what information we might collect from a registered user or other visitor (“you”), and what we will and will not do with it.  
Please note that this privacy policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that Complete Care Maintenance does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by Complete Care Maintenance. If you visit a Web site that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information.

### Your Privacy

* * *

Complete Care Maintenance follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. We utilize the Personal Data you offer in a way that is consistent with this Personal privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a particular reason, we could make use of the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For example, registration info sent when developing your account, might be used to assist suggest products to you based on past acquisitions. We might use your Personal Data to offer access to services on the Site and monitor your use of such services. Complete Care Maintenance may also utilize your Personal Data and various other personally non-identifiable info gathered through the Website to assist us improve the material and functionality of the Website, to much better comprehend our users, and to improve our services. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section below.

### Definitions

* * *

“Non Personal Information” is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser. It may also include publicly available information that is shared between you and others.

“Personally Identifiable Information” is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you within our Website. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your name, email address, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you.  
Information We Collect  
Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website. As a Visitor, you can browse our website to find out more about our Website. You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor.  
Computer Information Collected  
When you use our Website, we automatically collect certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website. Such information is typically considered Non Personal Information. We also collect the following:

### Cookies

* * *

Complete Care Maintenance uses “cookies” to store personal data on your computer. We may also link information stored on your computer in cookies with personal data about specific individuals stored on our servers. If you set up your Web browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Firefox) so that cookies are not allowed, you might not be able to use some or all of the features of our Web site(s).

### Geographical Information

* * *

When you use the mobile application, we may use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location in order to determine the city you are located within and display information with relevant data or advertisements. We will not share your current location with other users or partners. If you do not want us to use your location for the purposes set forth above, you should turn off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application.

### Automatic Information

* * *

We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.

### Log Data

* * *

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.  
Under the Child’s Online Privacy Security Act, no web site operator can require, as a condition to involvement in an activity, that a child younger than 13 years of age divulge more details than is reasonably required. Complete Care Maintenance abides by this demand. Complete Care Maintenance just collects information willingly offered; no information is gathered passively. children under 13 can submit only their email address when sending us an email in our “Contact Us” area. Complete Care Maintenance makes use of the e-mail address to respond to a one-time demand from a child under 13 and afterwards deletes the e-mail address. In case Complete Care Maintenance collects and maintains personal information relating to a child under 13, the parent may send out an email to us to review, alter and/or erase such info as well as to decline to enable any additional collection or use of the child’s information.

### What we do with your personally identifiable information

* * *

What we do with your personally identifiable information It is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services.

“Personally identifiable information” means information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as, for example:

  * your name, company, email address, phone number, billing address, and shipping address
  * your Complete Care Maintenance user ID and password (if applicable)
  * credit card information (if applicable)
  * any account-preference information you provide us
  * your computer’s domain name and IP address, indicating where your computer is located on the Internet
  * session data for your login session, so that our computer can ‘talk’ to yours while you are logged in If you do provide personally identifiable information to us, either directly or through a reseller or other business partner, we will:
  * not sell or rent it to a third party without your permission — although unless you opt out (see below), we may use your contact information to provide you with information we believe you need to know or may find useful, such as (for example) news about our services and products and modifications to the Terms of Service;
  * take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction;
  * not use or disclose the information except:
  * as necessary to provide services or products you have ordered, such as (for example) by providing it to a carrier to deliver products you have ordered;
  * in other ways described in this privacy policy or to which you have otherwise consented;
  * in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined (for example, statistical compilations);
  * as required by law, for example, in response to a subpoena or search warrant;
  * to outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential;
  * as necessary to enforce the Terms of Service;
  * as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of Complete Care Maintenance, its users, or others; this may include (for example) exchanging information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.

### Other information we collect

* * *

We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as (for example) the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of our Web site(s); research and development; customer- and account administration; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely.

### External data storage sites

* * *

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom  
we have contracted.

### Your privacy responsibilities

* * *

To help protect your privacy, be sure:

  * not to share your user ID or password with anyone else;
  * to log off the Complete Care Maintenance Web site when you are finished;
  * to take customary precautions to guard against “malware” (viruses, Trojan horses, bots,  
etc.), for example by installing and updating suitable anti-virus software.

### Notice to European Union users

* * *

Complete Care Maintenance‘s operations are located primarily in the United States. If you  
provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of the European Union  
(EU) to the United States. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to  
its storage and use as described herein.

### Information collected from children

* * *

You must be at least 13 years old to use Complete Care Maintenance‘s Web site(s) and service(s). Complete Care Maintenance does not knowingly collect information from children  
under 13. (See the [U.S.] Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.)

### Legally Required Releases of Information

* * *

We may be legally required to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of Complete Care Maintenance, our Users, employees, and affiliates.

### Opt Out

* * *

We offer you the chance to “opt-out” of having your personally identifiable information used for particular functions, when we ask you for this detail. When you register for the Site, if you do not want to receive any additional material or notifications from us, you can show your preference on our registration form.

### Links to Other Websites

* * *

Our Website may contain links to other websites that are not under our direct control. These websites may have their own policies regarding privacy. We have no control of or responsibility for linked websites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. You access such linked Websites at your own risk. These websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should check the privacy policies, if any, of those individual websites to see how the operators of those third-party websites will utilize your personal information. In addition, these websites may contain a link to Websites of our affiliates. The websites of our affiliates are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and you should check their individual privacy policies to see how the operators of such websites will utilize your personal information.

### Security

* * *

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We utilize practical protection measures to safeguard against the loss, abuse, and modification of the individual Data under our control. Personal Data is kept in a secured database and always sent out by means of an encrypted SSL method when supported by your web browser. No Web or e-mail transmission is ever totally protected or mistake cost-free. For example, email sent out to or from the Site may not be protected. You must take unique care in deciding what info you send to us by means of e-mail.

### Changes to this privacy policy

* * *

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. If you have provided us with an email address, we will endeavor to notify you, by email to that address, of any material change to how we will use personally identifiable information.

### Questions about our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy

* * *

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please contact us.
